(Penny:)Oh, my God.
(Penny:)What a day.
(Leonard:)Can I get you anything?
(Raj:)No.
(Penny:)I need to start
making some smart decisions.
(Leonard:)With your career?
(Penny:)With my life.
(Leonard:)Like what?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Penny:)We could get married.
(Leonard:)-Come on, be serious.
-I am.
(Leonard:)Why?
Because I'm a "smart decision"?
(Penny:)Well, yeah.
(Leonard:)So, I'm like a bran muffin.
What, no, that's not what I'm saying.
(Leonard:)No, it's exactly what you're saying.
I'm the boring thing
(Leonard:)you're choosing
because I'm good for you.
(Penny:)What does it matter?
The point is, I'm choosing you.
(Leonard:)Well, it matters a lot.
I don't want to be a bran muffin.
(Leonard:)I want to be a...
Cinnabon, you know?
(Leonard:)A strawberry Pop-Tart.